A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A94), 1966-1994; 1.20; 217.2 Cubic Feet; Record cartons R2728-R2895, R2880A, R2896-R2902, R2905, R2906-R2911, R9402 and R9403.
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 9013 - National Council of Educational Opportunity Associations - Student Leadership Conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9014 - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - "Facing History" on TV, 1990-1991 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9016 - Fund for Free Expression - Israel/Palestine conflict management, 1989-1992 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9018 - University of Chicago - "Managers of Science" book, 1990-1991 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9019 - National Academy of Public Administration - Public service commission, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9020 - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Mandela conversation, 1990-1991 (Box R2858)
    - SIE 9022 - Helsinki Assembly, 1990-1991 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9025 - French Institute of International Relations - Weapons proliferation, 1990-1994 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9027 - Africa Fund - "South Africa Now" TV programs, 1988-1992 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9028 - Cold Comfort Farm Trust - South Africa research, 1987-1992 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9031 - American Academy of Arts & Sciences - Research resources redeployment, 1990-1993 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9033 - Monterey Institute of International Studies - Ballistic missile trade, 1990-1991 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9038 - Independent Sector - Protect charitable deduction, 1990-1991 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9040 - Gerwel, C. Jakes, 1990 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9041 - Esquel Group Foundation - Ecuador Foundation, 1989-1993 (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9041 - Esquel Group Foundation - Ecuador Foundation - Supplementary material (Box R2859)
    - SIE 9042 - Parliamentarians for Global Action - "Moving the Test Ban to Center Stage", 1990-1992 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9043 - National Community AIDS partnership - Education and service programs, 1990-1993 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9044 - University ot Colorado - International School of Public Affairs, 1990-1992 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9046 - University of Witwatersrand - Public policy and development administration, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9047 - Partnership tor Democracy - Bannerman Memorial Fellowship Program, 1990-1991 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9051 - World Congress on Philanthropy Educational Foundation, 1990-1993 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9052 - Africa Resources Trust (England) - Southern African NGO Resource Centre, 1990-1992 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9055 - New York Communtty Trust - Funders concerned about AIDS, 1990-1992 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9056 - Mediators Foundation, Inc. - Partners Project, 1988-1994 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9057 - Wilton Park - Global Security conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9102 - National Academy of Public Administration - National Public Service Award, 1990-1991 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9107 - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation - Feasibility study, 1990-1992 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9108 - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Tennesee abortion laws and adolescents, 1990-1993 (Box R2860)
    - SIE 9110 - Chinese Scholars of Political Science and International Studies, Inc. - Sino-American relations, 1990-1992 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9112 - Harvard University - Domesticabuse programs test, 1990-1993 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9113 - City University of New York (CCNY) - Higher education careers brochure, 1991-1992 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9114 - African-American Institute, Inc. - South African Development Bank, 1990-1992 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9115 - ArtsConnection - ArtsCenter, 1991-1993 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9116 - National Civic League - Political competitiveness and term limitation, 1991-1991 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9117 - American Institutes for Research (in the Behavioral Sciences) - Social Services planning conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9120 - Princeton University Press - Einstein collected papers, 1991 (Box R2861)
    - SIE 9121 - Foundation for New Philanthropy, Inc. - Increasing programmatic reach, 1990-1992 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9122 - New York Community Trust -NewYork City youth recreation and employment programs, 1991-1993 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9123 - University of California (Irvine) - Education conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9124 - Common Cents New York, Inc., 1991-1992 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9125 - CEIP Fund, Inc. - Focus on Non profits, 1989-1992 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9126 - Partnership for a Drug-Free America - Inner-City initiative, 1991-1994 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9127 - Council on Addiction and Substance Abuse - Development Planning, 1991-1994 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9129 - University of Georgia - Dean and Virginia Rusk Fund, 1990-1991 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9130 - Asia Society - Asian American experience conference, 1991-1993 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9131 - Corporation for Supportive Housing - New York City program, 1991-1992 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9134 - Independent Sector - International Networking, 1991 (Box R2862)
    - SIE 9140 - Farmworker Justice Fund, Inc. - "H-2 Worker" broadcast, 1991-1992 (Box R2863)
    - SIE 9141 - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility - 21st Century project, 1990-1992 (Box R2863)
    - SIE 9142 - Communications Consortium - Communications advice for nonprofit organizations, 1991-1993 (Box R2863)
    - SIE 9148 - Lawyer's Committee for Human Rights - Rule of law in the Middle East, 1991-1993 (Box R2863)
  - Special Programming (SP)
    - SP 8701 - National Academy of Sciences - Role of science and technology in development conference, 1987-1988, 1994 (Box R2863)
    - SP 8709 - Ethonographic Institute - Co-evolutionary terrains, 1986-1993 (Box R2863)
    - SP 8709 - Ethonographic Institute - Co-evolutionary terrains - Supplementary materials (Box R2863)
    - SP 8710 - Scientific Information and Communication Systems for Third World Science Based Development - Conference, 1987-1989, 1994 (Box R2863)
    - SP 8806 - Scientific Literacy in African Primary Schools - Conference, 1987-1990, 1994 (Box R2863)
    - SP 8813 - University of California (San Francisco) - World molecular engineering network, 1988-1990 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8814 - Scripps Clinic & Research Foundation - World Molecular Engineering Network, 1988-1991 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8816 - British Medical Association - Nuffield Library bibliometric study, 1988-1991 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8817 - Scripps Clinic & Research Foundation - Cell biological function meeting, 1988, 1991-1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8819 - British Medical Research Council - World Molecular Engineering Network, 1988-1990 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8821 - International Extension College (London) - Evaluation of the Third World education, 1988-1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8824 - RF Exploration on Science & Technology in the Popular Culture, 1988-1990 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8827 - Institute for International Economics - Trade policies and linkages, 1988-1989, 1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8832 - New York Academy of Sciences - Biomedical conference proceedings, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8833 - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies (Singapore) - Scientific & Technological revolution, 1988-1991 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8836 - National Polytechnic Institute (Mexico City) - Biomedical Conference spanish proceedings, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8840 - Ethics & Public Policy Center - Islam conflict resolution, 1988-1992 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8841 - Johns Hopkins University - Political economy of African countries, 1988-1991 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8903 - Aga Khan Foundation U.S.A. - Microcomputers in education assessment (Kenya), 1987-1994 (Box R2864)
    - SP 8908 - Tata Energy Research Institute - Information and Research Centre, 1989-1993 (Box R2865)
    - SP 8911 - Worldwatch Institute - Environmental development, 1989-1992 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9002 - University of Lagos - "Science & technology education in Africa" book, 1990 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9003 - City University of New York - Bouchet conference on physics & technology in Ghana, 1990-1993 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9005 - World Bank - African education donors information, 1989-1990 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9006 - Cornell University - African child mortality, 1987-1993 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9008 - International Development Conference - from cold war to cooperation, 1990-1991 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9010 - International African Institute, London - Healing social wounds of war conference, 1990-1991 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9012 - African Academy of Sciences - African Foundation for Research & Development, 1990-1992 (Box R2865)
    - SP 9102 - African Academy of Sciences - Pan African Congress of Mathematicians, 1991-1992 (Box R2866)
  - African Initiatives (AI)
    - AI 9107 - Council for the Development of Ecomomic and Social Research in Africa - Agrarian chanqe, 1991-1993 (Box R2866)
    - AI 9108 - Columbia University - Narmanda Valley Development Project conference, 1991-1992 (Box R2866)
    - AI 9109 - University of Ibadan - Travel costs to African economic conference (Lome, Togo, 1992 June), 1991-1993 (Box R2866)
    - AI 9110 - University of Florida- Impact of Structural Adjustment on Agriculture, 1991-1992 (Box R2866)
    - AI 9112 - University of Nairobi - Seminar on effect of structural adjustment on Kenyan women (1992 March 4-7), 1991-1992 (Box R2866)
  - School Reform (SR)
    - SR 9001 - Committe for Economic Development - Education and Child Development, 1989-1991 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9004 - Rockefeller Foundation Institute of Community and Actions Projects - Proceedings, 1990 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9006 - Comer Campaign, 1992 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9007 - Public Education Association - "New Schools for New York", 1989-1993 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9008 - San Diego City Schools - Demonstration Leadership Academy, 1990-1993 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9009 - National Council of La Raza - Education reform, 1990-1992 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9012 - New Haven Public Schools - Summer Training Institute, 1990-1993 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9013 - Education Commission of the States - Education Leaders Meeting, 1990-1992 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9014 - University of New Mexico - National Laboratories Leaders Conference, 1990 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9015 - Educational Consortium of Central Los Angeles - Disadvantaged Students Program, 1990 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9017 - "The Juice Factory" - At-risk urban youth program, 1989-1992 (Box R2871)
    - SR 9018 - Artists Space - TeachingTV, 1990-1993 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9019 - Central State University - Graduate School Courses, 1990 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9101 - National Council of La Raza - Education Reform Policy Analysis, 1990-1991 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9102 - Council of Chief State School Officers - Video Series, 1990, 1993 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9104 - College Board - "Juice Factory", 1990-1991 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9105 - Efficacy Institute, Inc. - Development And Training, 1990-1994 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9107 - Council of Michigan Foundations - Information Exchange Service, 1990-1992 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9108 - Council on Foundations - Grantmakers for Children and Youth, 1990-1992 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9109 - Learning Channel - "Learning Matters: In Focus", 1990-1991 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9110 - Harvard University - Feasibility Study, 1989-1993 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9113 - Alliance for Education in Global and International Studies (AEGEIS ) - Program Development, 1991 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9114 - EVT Productions, Inc. - Conference Taping, 1990-1991 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9115 - The Factory - Development and Implementation, 1991-1992 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9120 - "Juice Factory" - Program Development, 1990-1992 (Box R2872)
    - SR 9121 - Michigan State University Graduate Schools of Education Project, 1991-1992 (Box R2873)
    - SR 9123 - Fund For The City of New York Commissioners Retreat, 1991-1993 (Box R2873)
    - SR 9126 - Coalition of Community Foundations For Youth - Conference, 1991-1994 (Box R2873)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A95), 1984-1994; 1.21; 13.2 Cubic Feet; 11 record cartons. Boxes R2912-R2915, R2918-R2924.
  Arranged by Program.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 91067 A 3 - Hammarskjold Foundation - Africa - African Publishers Fund, 1991-1992 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91067 A 5 - Obor, Inc. - Distribute Publishing and Development in the Third World in Africa, 1992-1994 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91067 A 7 - Canadian Organization for Develoment through Education - 1992 Conference on Establishment of African Publishing Institute (Box R2912)
    - RF 91067 A 9 - Canadian Organization for Development Through Education - Donors Workshops, 1992 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91068 A 85 - Cheang, Shu Lea, 1989-1993 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91068 A 86 - Mekas, Jonas, 1989-1994 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91068 A 88 - Whitney Museum of American Art - Remapping Culture(s): Film and the Media Arts, 1992-1994 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91068 A 103 - Latin American Committee of Indigenous Peoples' Films - Inter-American Film festival, 1991-1993 (Box R2912)
    - RF 91069 - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. - Alive from Off Center, 1985-1992; 2 folders. (Box R2912)
    - RF 91069 - Twin Cities Public Television, Inc. - Alive from Off Center - Supplementary material (Box R2912)
    - RF 91071 A 44 - Greater Washington Research Center - Committee for D.C., 1984-1993; 5 folders. (Box R2913)
    - RF 91071 A 44 - Greater Washington Research Center - Committee for D.C., 1984-1993; 2 folders. (Box R2914)
    - RF 91071 A 44 - Greater Washington Research Center - Committee for D.C. - Supplementary material, 3 folders. (Box R2914)
    - RF 91071 A 44 - Greater Washington Research Center - Committee for D.C. - Supplementary material, 3 folders. (Box R2915)
    - RF 91071 A 54 - Piton Foundaiton - 1990 Census data and local earned income tax credit campaign, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box R2918)
    - RF 91077 A 1 - International Service for the Acquisition of Agri-Biotech Applications (ISAAA) - Workshop on Biosafety, 1991-1993 (Box R2918)
    - RF 91077 A 2 - Mpepereki, Sheunesu- Attend workshop at Michigan State University, 1992-1993 (Box R2918)
    - RF 91079 A 29 - Thai Red Cross Society - Commercial sex workers and HIV transmission pilot study, 1991-1994 (Box R2918)
    - RF 91079 A 38 - Human Rights Project, Inc. - Developing country participation in AIDS forum, 1992 (Box R2918)
    - RF 91085 - Columbia University - Family planning technical assistance to African institutions, 1984-1994 (Box R2919)
    - RF 91086 A 8 - Cornell University - Multilateral Process for Global Environment Analysis, 1991-1993 (Box R2919)
    - RF 91086 A 10 - Foundation for Environmental Development and Education in Nigeria (FEDEN) - Seminar on Population, Environment and Development, 1992 (Box R2919)
    - RF 91090 A 68 - Nwokedi, Obunikem C. - Writing Project: "Democratic transition in Nigeria and Benin", 1991-1992 (Box R2919)
    - RF 91090 A 69 - Chafe, Kabiru Sulaiman - Writing project on Islam's impact in Nigeria, 1991-1993 (Box R2919)
    - RF 91090 A 70 - Elmekki, Abdelgalil, Mahdi Food insecurity in Sudan, 1991-1992 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91090 A 71 - Institute for Southeast Asia Studies - Reflections on Development workshop, 1991-1992 (Box R2920)
      For 1992 September conference.
    - RF 91090 A 73 - Shivji, Issa Gulamhussein - "Rule of Law and Ujamaa in Ideological Formation of Tanzania", 1991-1992 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91090 A 75 - Hartmann, Jeannette - Writing project "The Nyerere State", 1991-1992 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91094 - Meet the Composer - Jazz composer fellowships, 1988-1993 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91095 A 75 - American Indian Community House, Inc. - "Coatlicue/Las Colorado", 1991-1993 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91095 A 80 - Crossroads, Inc. - "The Love Space Demands", 1991-1993 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91095 A 82 - Idris Ackamoor & Cultural odyssey - "Emergency report", 1991-1993 (Box R2920)
    - RF 91095 A 83 - Dance Brigade - "White Winged Mercy", 1991-1994 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91095 A 85 - Dar a luz - Production of "Law of Remains", 1991-1993 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91095 A 89 - La Mama Experimental Theater Club, Inc. - "Point of Debarkation", 1991-1993 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91095 A 92 - Climate Theatre - "The Queen's Garden", 1991-1994 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91095 A 93 - American Jazz Theatre - "Millenium", 1991-1994 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 - Civil Rights Litigation Organization, 1989-1993 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 - Civil Rights Litigation Organization - Supplementary material (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 A 1 - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Computerizing its scholarship and fundraising programs, 1991-1993 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 A 2 - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund (MALDEF) - Direct mail campaigns, 1991 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 A 3 - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - Enhance fundraising capabilities, 1991-1992 (Box R2921)
    - RF 91097 A 4 - Puetro Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund - Technical assistance, 1992 (Box R2921)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - New School vs. NEA - Briefing Materials, Vol 1. (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - New School vs. NEA - Briefing Materials, Vol 2. (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Controversy, 1993 (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Documents - Back up copy (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - GAO Report (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Section 304 (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Controversy, 1990 (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Controversy, 1990 (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Reauthorization (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Testimonies: Frohnmayer; Goldmark; Levitt (Box R2922)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - Finley vs. NEA - Briefs, 1993 June (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - Finley vs. NEA (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - Finley vs. NEA (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Committee/John Brademas (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Rust vs. Sullivan (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - National Access Project (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - AMICUS CURIAE Brief (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Julianne Ross Davis (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Coleman-Williams Amendment (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Responses/RF Grantees, 1990 (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Bella Lewitzky (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Controversy: Overview materials (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Grantee Updates, 1990 September 8 (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - RF Grantee Memorandum (Box R2923)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Documents: Originals (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Certification Requirements (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Press Clippings (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Frankie FitzGerald (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - The New School/J. Fanton (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Activity (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA/The New School (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Independent Commission, 1990 July 23 (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Independent Commission (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Independent Commission/ABA Testimony (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Independent Commission (Box R2924)
    - RF 89065 - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art - Artists Fellowships - NEA - Independent Commission (Box R2924)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A96), 1965-1996; bulk; 1.22; 50.4 Cubic Feet; 42 record cartons. Boxes R2925-R2694.
  Arranged primarily by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure, with some materials arranged by Program.
  - CGIAR, 104
    - AGRICULTURAL INSTITUTES (CGIAR), 1983-1989 (Box R2940)
  - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 105
    - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER, 1983-1991 (Box R2940)
    - DONATION OF EQUIPMENT, 1983-1984 (Box R2940)
  - ISNAR, 111
    - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (ISNAR), 1984-1990 (Box R2940)
    - MERRILL-SANDS, DEBORAH M., 1985-1988 (Box R2941)
    - MERRILL-SANDS, DEBORAH M. - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2 folders. (Box R2941)
  - ILRAD, 112
    - INTERNATIONAL LABORATORY FOR RESEARCH ON ANIMAL DISEASES (ILRAD), 1984-1989 (Box R2941)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 115
    - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE, 1983-1990 (Box R2941)
    - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE - GOLDMAN, 1983-1989 (Box R2941)
  - ICRISAT, 116
    - INTERNATIONAL CROPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR THE SEMI-ARID TROPICS (ICRISAT), 1982-1991, 1995 (Box R2942)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2016. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
  - ICIPE, 117
    - INTERNATIONAL CENTER OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (ICIPE), 1983-1990 (Box R2942)
    - INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT SERVICE) - BOARD OF TRUSTEES, 1977-1982 (Box R2942)
    - INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT SERVICE - BOARD OF TRUSTEES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1977-1982 (Box R2942)
  - IADS, 119
    - IADS - MINUTES, 1975-1985 (Box R2942)
    - IADS - ORGANIZATION AND PLANNING, 1980-1985 (Box R2942)
    - IADS - ORGANIZATION AND PLANNING, 1973-1975, 1976-1979; 4 folders. (Box R2943)
    - IADS - ORGANIZATION AND PLANNING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 2 folders. (Box R2943)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - ADVANCED DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - TECHNICAL COOPERATION AND GLOBAL CLIMATE CHANGE - CONFERENCE, 1990-1992 (Box R2925)
    - AFRICAN CULTURE - CONFERENCE, 1985-1988, 1991 (Box R2925)
    - AFRICAN SCIENTIFIC INSTITUTION BUILDING - CONFERENCE, 1987-1989 (Box R2925)
    - AGRICULTURAL POLICIES FOR DEVELOPING COUNTRIES FOR 1990's, 1990-1994 (Box R2925)